Guide to the Poetry: A Magazine of Verse Records 1895-1961
University of Chicago Library
- Series IV: Oversize
  - Subseries 1: Administrative Files, 1912-1936
    - Sub-subseries 2: Major Poets
      - Ernest Walsh, Poem, "White Spiders" Last Will and testament of EW appointing HM his literary executor (Box 162, Folder 33)
      - John Hall Wheelock, galley, "Night has Its Fears" (Box 162, Folder 34)
      - Frank Lloyd Wright to HM, nd (Box 162, Folder 35)
      - William Butler Yeats, reviews and obituary (Box 162, Folder 36)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Addenda
      - Guarantor files, receipt, 24 Sep 1919 (financial records) (Box 162, Folder 37)
      - Financial reports, 1913-1933 (Box 162, Folder 38)
      - News clipping, obituary for Miss Harriet Monroe (Box 162, Folder 39)
      - Clippings, A (Box 162, Folder 40)
      - Clippings, B (Box 162, Folder 41)
      - Clippings, C (Box 163, Folder 1-2)
      - Clippings, D (Box 163, Folder 3)
      - Clippings, F (Box 163, Folder 4)
      - Clippings, G (Box 163, Folder 5)
      - Clippings, H (Box 163, Folder 6)
      - Clippings, I (Box 163, Folder 7)
      - Clippings, J (Box 163, Folder 8)
      - Clippings, L (Box 163, Folder 9-11)
      - Clippings, M (Box 163, Folder 12-15)
      - Clippings, N (Box 163, Folder 16)
      - Clippings, P (Box 163, Folder 17-28)
      - Clippings, P (Box 164, Folder 1)
      - Clippings, R (Box 164, Folder 2)
      - Clippings, S (Box 164, Folder 3)
      - Clippings, S (Box 164, Folder 4)
      - Clippings, S (Box 164, Folder 5)
      - Clippings, T (Box 164, Folder 6)
      - Clippings, U-V (Box 164, Folder 7)
      - Clippings, W (Box 164, Folder 8)
      - Clippings, X-Z (Box 164, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 2: Administrative Files, 1936-1953
    - Sub-subseries 1: Manuscripts - Major Contributors
      - Abse, Dannie (Box 164, Folder 10)
      - Anderson, Patrick (Box 164, Folder 11)
      - Auden, W. H. (Box 164, Folder 12)
      - Caffrey, John (Box 164, Folder 13)
      - cummings, e. e. (Box 164, Folder 14)
      - Dahlberg, Edward (Box 164, Folder 15)
      - Dahlberg, Edward (Box 164, Folder 16)
      - Daiches, David (Box 164, Folder 17)
      - Dillon, George (Box 164, Folder 18)
      - Dillon, George (Box 164, Folder 19)
      - Duncan, Harry (Box 164, Folder 20)
      - Eberhart, Richard (Box 164, Folder 21)
      - Eliot, T. S. (Box 164, Folder 22)
      - Fitts, Dudley (Box 164, Folder 23)
      - Fletcher, John Gould (Box 164, Folder 24)
      - Friar, Kimon (Box 164, Folder 25)
      - Goodman, Paul (Box 165, Folder 1)
      - Hays, H.R. (Box 165, Folder 2)
      - Thomas Howells (Box 165, Folder 3)
      - Jeffers, Robinson (Box 165, Folder 4)
      - Jimenez, Juan Ramon (Box 165, Folder 5)
      - Jolas, Eugene (Box 165, Folder 6)
      - Logan, John (Box 165, Folder 7)
      - MacLeish, Archibald (Box 165, Folder 8)
      - Morse,Samuel French (Box 165, Folder 9)
      - Roditi, Edouard (Box 165, Folder 10)
      - Scott, Winfield Townley (Box 165, Folder 11)
      - Stevens, Wallace (Box 165, Folder 12)
      - Taggard, Genevieve (Box 165, Folder 13)
      - Warren, Robert Penn (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Manuscripts - Minor Contributors
      - Davis, Betty Miller (Box 165, Folder 15)
      - Hodgson, Ralph (Box 165, Folder 16)
      - Sullivan, A. M. (Box 165, Folder 17)
      - Valéry, Paul (Box 165, Folder 18)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Editorial Files
      - April, 1938 (Box 165, Folder 19)
      - October 1939 (Box 165, Folder 20)
      - September 1939 (Box 165, Folder 21)
      - November 1939 (Box 165, Folder 22)
      - September 1943 (Box 165, Folder 23)
      - February 1951 (Box 165, Folder 24)
      - March 1951 (Box 165, Folder 25)
      - February 1952 (Box 165, Folder 26)
      - March 1952 (Box 165, Folder 27)
      - September 1952 (Box 165, Folder 28)
      - October, 1952 (Box 165, Folder 29)
      - September 1953 (Box 165, Folder 30)
    - Sub-subseries 4: Business Files
      - Advertisers, S (Box 166, Folder 1)
      - Other Organizations, P (Box 166, Folder 2)
      - Printing and design correspondence (Box 166, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous Business Correspondence 1938-1944 (Box 166, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous Business Correspondence 1949-1950 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 3: Administrative Files, 1954-1961
    - Sub-subseries 1: Contributors - Manuscripts and Correspondence
      - Adams, Léonie (Box 166, Folder 6)
      - Alvarez, A (Box 166, Folder 7)
      - Ammons, A. R. (Box 166, Folder 8)
      - Ashbery, John (Box 166, Folder 9)
      - Avison, Margaret (Box 166, Folder 10)
      - Bagg, Robert (Box 166, Folder 11)
      - Barker, George (Box 166, Folder 12)
      - Baro, Gene (Box 166, Folder 13)
      - Basler, Roy (Box 166, Folder 14)
      - Belitt, Ben (Box 166, Folder 15)
      - Belitt, Ben (Box 166, Folder 16)
      - Belvin, William (Box 166, Folder 17)
      - Bennett, Joseph (Box 166, Folder 18)
      - Bergholz, Harry (Box 166, Folder 19)
      - Berlind, Bruce (Box 166, Folder 20)
      - Berrigan, Daniel (Box 166, Folder 21)
      - Berry, John (Box 166, Folder 22)
      - Berry, Wendell (Box 166, Folder 23)
      - Berry, Wendell (Box 166, Folder 24)
      - Berryman, John (Box 166, Folder 25)
      - Beum, Robert (Box 166, Folder 26)
      - Birnbaum, Henry (Box 166, Folder 27)
      - Birnbaum, Henry (Box 166, Folder 28)
      - Birnbaum, Henry (Box 166, Folder 29)
      - Bishop, Elizabeth (Box 166, Folder 30)
      - Blum, Etta (Box 166, Folder 31)
      - Bly, Robert (Box 166, Folder 32)
      - Bock, Frederick (Box 166, Folder 33)
      - Bode, Carl (Box 166, Folder 34)
      - Bogardus, Edgar (Box 166, Folder 35)
      - Booth, Philip (Box 166, Folder 36)
      - Booth, Philip (Box 166, Folder 37)
      - Broughton, James (Box 167, Folder 1)
      - Br- (Box 167, Folder 2)
      - Burden, Jean (Box 167, Folder 3)
      - Burford, William (Box 167, Folder 4)
      - Burke, Kenneth (Box 167, Folder 5)
      - Burke, Kenneth (Box 167, Folder 6)
      - Burr, Gray (Box 167, Folder 7)
      - Burrows, E. G. (Box 167, Folder 8)
      - Burtle, Mary (Mary Erulkar) (Box 167, Folder 9)
      - Bynner, Witter (Box 167, Folder 10)
      - Cambon, Glauco (Box 167, Folder 11)
      - Cameron, J. M. (Box 167, Folder 12)
      - Campbell, Roy (Box 167, Folder 13)
      - Cargill, Oscar (Box 167, Folder 14)
      - Carrier, Warren (Box 167, Folder 15)
      - Carruth, Hayden (Box 167, Folder 16)
      - Carruth, Hayden (Box 167, Folder 17)
      - Carruth, Hayden (Box 167, Folder 18)
      - Carruth, Hayden (Box 167, Folder 19)
      - Carruth, Hayden (Box 167, Folder 20)
      - Carruth, Hayden (Box 167, Folder 21)
      - Carruth, Hayden (Box 167, Folder 22)
      - Carruth, Hayden (Box 167, Folder 23)
      - Carruth, Hayden (Box 167, Folder 24)
      - Cassity, Turner (Box 167, Folder 25)
      - Ciardi, John (Box 167, Folder 26)
      - Clower, Jean (Box 167, Folder 27)
      - Coleman, Elliott (Box 167, Folder 28)
      - Copley, Frank O. (Box 167, Folder 29)
      - Coxe, Louis O. (Box 167, Folder 30)
      - Coxe, Louis O. (Box 167, Folder 31)
      - Coxe, Louis O. (Box 167, Folder 32)
      - Craig, Alexander (Box 167, Folder 33)
      - Creeley, Robert (Box 167, Folder 34)
      - Creeley, Robert (Box 167, Folder 35)
      - Creeley, Robert (Box 167, Folder 36)
      - cummings, e. e. (Box 167, Folder 37)
      - Cutler, Bruce (Box 167, Folder 38)
      - Dahlberg, Edward (Box 167, Folder 39)
      - Dalven, Rae (Box 167, Folder 40)
      - Dana, Robert (Box 167, Folder 41)
      - Davie, Donald (Box 167, Folder 42)
      - Decavalles, Andonis (Box 167, Folder 43)
      - DeJong, David Cornel (Box 167, Folder 44)
      - DeJong, David Cornel (Box 167, Folder 45)
      - Denny, Reuel (Box 168, Folder 1)
      - Denny, Reuel (Box 168, Folder 2)
      - Denny, Reuel (Box 168, Folder 3)
      - Deutsch, Babette (Box 168, Folder 4)
      - Deutsch, Babette (Box 168, Folder 5)
      - Dickey, James, poetry (Box 168, Folder 6)
      - Dickey, James, poetry (Box 168, Folder 7)
      - Dickey, James, poetry (Box 168, Folder 8)
      - Dickey, James, poetry (Box 168, Folder 9)
      - Dickey, James, prose (Box 168, Folder 10)
      - Dickey, James, prose (Box 168, Folder 11)
      - Dickey, William (Box 168, Folder 12)
      - Dickey, William (Box 168, Folder 13)
      - Dillon, George (Box 168, Folder 14)
      - Donnelly, Dorothy (Box 168, Folder 15)
      - Donnelly, Dorothy (Box 168, Folder 16)
      - Donnelly, Dorothy (Box 168, Folder 17)
      - Donoghue, Denis (Box 168, Folder 18)
      - Doolittle, Hilda (H. D.) (Box 168, Folder 19)
      - Dugan, Alan (Box 168, Folder 20)
      - Duncan, Harry (Box 168, Folder 21)
      - Duncan, Robert (Box 168, Folder 22)
      - Duncan, Robert (Box 168, Folder 23)
      - Duncan, Robert (Box 168, Folder 24)
      - Duncan, Robert (Box 168, Folder 25)
      - Duncan, Robert (Box 168, Folder 26)
      - Dunetz, Lora (Box 168, Folder 27)
      - Eberhart, Richard (Box 168, Folder 28)
      - Eberhart, Richard (Box 168, Folder 29)
      - Eberhart, Richard (Box 168, Folder 30)
      - Eckman, Frederick (Box 168, Folder 31)
      - Edwards, John (Box 168, Folder 32)
      - Elmslie, Kenward (Box 168, Folder 33)
      - Ely, Gladys (Box 168, Folder 34)
      - Engels, John (Box 168, Folder 35)
      - Engle, Paul (Box 168, Folder 36)
      - English, Maurice (Box 168, Folder 37)
      - Everson, Ronald (Box 168, Folder 38)
      - Fiedler, Leslie (Box 168, Folder 39)
      - Finkel, Donald (Box 168, Folder 40)
      - Fitts, Dudley (Box 168, Folder 41)
      - Fitts, Dudley (Box 168, Folder 42)
      - Fitzgerald, Gerald (Box 169, Folder 1)
      - Fleming, Harold (Box 169, Folder 2)
      - Fowlie, Wallace (Box 169, Folder 3)
      - Fowlie, Wallace (Box 169, Folder 4)
      - Fowlie, Wallace (Box 169, Folder 5)
      - Fowlie, Wallace (Box 169, Folder 6)
      - Fowlie, Wallace (Box 169, Folder 7)
      - Fowlie, Wallace (Box 169, Folder 8)
      - Fowlie, Wallace (Box 169, Folder 9)
      - Fraser, G. S. (Box 169, Folder 10)
      - Friar, Kimon (Box 169, Folder 11)
      - Frumkin, Gene (Box 169, Folder 12)
      - Galler, David (Box 169, Folder 13)
      - Galler, David (Box 169, Folder 14)
      - Galler, David (Box 169, Folder 15)
      - Garrigue, Jean (Box 169, Folder 16)
      - Garrigue, Jean (Box 169, Folder 17)
      - Garrigue, Jean (Box 169, Folder 18)
      - Gibbs, Barbara (Box 169, Folder 19)
      - Gibbs, Barbara (Box 169, Folder 20)
      - Gifford, Henry (Box 169, Folder 21)
      - Gill, John J. (Box 169, Folder 22)
      - Gokak, V. K. (Box 169, Folder 23)
      - Golffing, Francis (Box 169, Folder 24)
      - Goodman, Paul (Box 169, Folder 25)
      - Goodman, Paul (Box 169, Folder 26)
      - Goodman, Paul (Box 169, Folder 27)
      - Gregor, Arthur (Box 169, Folder 28)
      - Gregor, Arthur (Box 169, Folder 29)
      - Gregory, Horace (Box 169, Folder 30)
      - Guenther, Charles (Box 169, Folder 31)
      - Gunn, Thom (Box 169, Folder 32)
      - Gunn, Thom (Box 169, Folder 33)
      - Gunn, Thom (Box 169, Folder 34)
      - Gunn, Thom (Box 169, Folder 35)
      - Hale, Nancy (Box 169, Folder 36)
      - Hall, Donald (Box 169, Folder 37)
      - Hall, Donald (Box 169, Folder 38)
      - Hamburger, Michael (Box 169, Folder 39)
      - Hanson, Pauline (Box 169, Folder 40)
      - Hardy, John Edward (Box 169, Folder 41)
      - Hart, Lawrence (Box 169, Folder 42)
      - Hartman, Geoffrey (Box 169, Folder 43)
      - Hazel, Robert (Box 170, Folder 1)
      - Henley, Elizabeth (Box 170, Folder 2)
      - Herschberger, Ruth (Box 170, Folder 3)
      - Hine, Daryl (Box 170, Folder 4)
      - Hollander, John (Box 170, Folder 5)
      - Hollander, John (Box 170, Folder 6)
      - Holmes, John (Box 170, Folder 7)
      - Holmes, Theodore (Box 170, Folder 8)
      - Holmes, Theodore (Box 170, Folder 9)
      - Honig, Edwin (Box 170, Folder 10)
      - Hooper, Patricia (Box 170, Folder 11)
      - Hoskins, Katherine (Box 170, Folder 12)
      - Howes, Barbara (Box 170, Folder 13)
      - Huff, Robert (Box 170, Folder 14)
      - Hughes, Ted (Box 170, Folder 15)
      - Hugo, Richard F. (Box 170, Folder 16)
      - Hu-Hy (Box 170, Folder 17)
      - Hull, Ora May (Box 170, Folder 18)
      - Humphries, Rolfe (Box 170, Folder 19)
      - Ignatow, David (Box 170, Folder 20)
      - Jacobsen, Josephine (Box 170, Folder 21)
      - Jacobsen, Josephine (Box 170, Folder 22)
      - Johnson, Carol (Box 170, Folder 23)
      - Johnson, W. R. (Box 170, Folder 24)
      - Jones, David (Box 170, Folder 25)
      - Justice, Donald (Box 170, Folder 26)
      - Justice, Donald (Box 170, Folder 27)
      - Kallman, Chester (Box 170, Folder 28)
      - Kennedy, X. J. (Box 170, Folder 29)
      - Kennedy, X. J. (Box 170, Folder 30)
      - Kenner, Hugh (Box 170, Folder 31)
      - Kenner, Hugh (Box 170, Folder 32)
      - Kenner, Hugh (Box 170, Folder 33)
      - Kenner, Hugh (Box 170, Folder 34)
      - Kenner, Hugh (Box 170, Folder 35)
      - Kenner, Hugh (Box 170, Folder 36)
      - Kenner, Hugh (Box 170, Folder 37)
      - Kenner, Hugh (Box 170, Folder 38)
      - Kenner, Hugh (Box 170, Folder 39)
      - Kessler, Jascha (Box 170, Folder 40)
      - Kinnell, Galway (Box 170, Folder 41)
      - Kinnell, Galway (Box 170, Folder 42)
      - Hazel, Robert (Box 170, Folder 43)
      - Kizer, Carolyn (Box 171, Folder 1)
      - Kizer, Carolyn (Box 171, Folder 2)
      - Kizer, Carolyn (Box 171, Folder 3)
      - Knoepfle, John (Box 171, Folder 4)
      - Koch, Kenneth (Box 171, Folder 5)
      - Koch, Kenneth (Box 171, Folder 6)
      - Koch, Vivienne (Box 171, Folder 7)
      - Kumin, Maxine (Box 171, Folder 8)
      - Kunitz, Stanley (Box 171, Folder 9)
      - Kunitz, Stanley (Box 171, Folder 10)
      - Lang, V. R. (Box 171, Folder 11)
      - Lattimore, Richmond (Box 171, Folder 12)
      - Lee, Peter (Box 171, Folder 13)
      - Legler, Philip (Box 171, Folder 14)
      - Levertov, Denise (Box 171, Folder 15)
      - Levertov, Denise (Box 171, Folder 16)
      - Levine, Philip (Box 171, Folder 17)
      - Levine, Rosalind (Box 171, Folder 18)
      - Lindeman, galley, review (Box 171, Folder 19)
      - Lipton, Lawrence (Box 171, Folder 20)
      - Logan, John (Box 171, Folder 21)
      - Lowell, Robert (Box 171, Folder 22)
      - Lowell, Robert (Box 171, Folder 23)
      - MacGreevy, Thomas (Box 171, Folder 24)
      - MacGreevy, Thomas (Box 171, Folder 25)
      - MacPherson, Jay (Box 171, Folder 26)
      - MacPherson, Jay (Box 171, Folder 27)
      - MacSherry, Charles W. (Box 171, Folder 28)
      - Mandelbaum, Allen (Box 171, Folder 29)
      - Mandelbaum, Allen (Box 171, Folder 30)
      - Mandelbaum, Allen (Box 171, Folder 31)
      - Marz, Roy (Box 171, Folder 32)
      - Marz, Roy (Box 171, Folder 33)
      - Masters, Marcia (Box 171, Folder 34)
      - McCormick, John (Box 171, Folder 35)
      - McGahey, Jeanne (Box 171, Folder 36)
      - McRobbie, Kenneth (Box 171, Folder 37)
      - McRobbie, Kenneth (Box 171, Folder 38)
      - Mercier, Vivian (Box 171, Folder 39)
      - Mercier, Vivian (Box 171, Folder 40)
      - Mercier, Vivian (Box 171, Folder 41)
      - Meredith, William (Box 171, Folder 42)
      - Meredith, William (Box 171, Folder 43)
      - Merrill, James (Box 171, Folder 44)
      - Merrill, James (Box 171, Folder 45)
      - Merrill, James (Box 171, Folder 46)
      - Merrill, James (Box 171, Folder 47)
      - Merrill, James (Box 171, Folder 48)
      - Merwin, W. S. (Box 171, Folder 49)
      - Merwin, W. S. (Box 171, Folder 50)
      - Merwin, W. S. (Box 171, Folder 51)
      - Miles, Josephine (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - Miller, Peter (Box 172, Folder 2)
      - Mills, Ralph (Box 172, Folder 3)
      - Milne, Ewart (Box 172, Folder 4)
      - Mohammed, Faqir (Box 172, Folder 5)
      - Montague, John (Box 172, Folder 6)
      - Montague, John (Box 172, Folder 7)
      - Montague, John (Box 172, Folder 8)
      - Montale, Eugenio (Box 172, Folder 9)
      - Montale, Eugenio (Box 172, Folder 10)
      - Montale, Eugenio (Box 172, Folder 11)
      - Montale, Eugenio (Box 172, Folder 12)
      - Moore, Marianne (Box 172, Folder 13)
      - Moore, Rosalie (Box 172, Folder 14)
      - Moore, Rosalie (Box 172, Folder 15)
      - Moore, Rosalie (Box 172, Folder 16)
      - Moore, Rosalie (Box 172, Folder 17)
      - Morgan, Frederick (Box 172, Folder 18)
      - Morris, Herbert (Box 172, Folder 19)
      - Morris, Herbert (Box 172, Folder 20)
      - Morris, Herbert (Box 172, Folder 21)
      - Morris, Herbert (Box 172, Folder 22)
      - Morris, Herbert (Box 172, Folder 23)
      - Morris, Herbert (Box 172, Folder 24)
      - Morse, Samuel French (Box 172, Folder 25)
      - Morse, Samuel French (Box 172, Folder 26)
      - Morse, Samuel French (Box 172, Folder 27)
      - Morse, Samuel French (Box 172, Folder 28)
      - Moss, Howard (Box 172, Folder 29)
      - Moss, Stanley (Box 172, Folder 30)
      - Mueller, Lisel (Box 172, Folder 31)
      - Murray, Philip (Box 172, Folder 32)
      - Myers, E. Lucas (Box 172, Folder 33)
      - Nathan, Leonard (Box 172, Folder 34)
      - Nathan, Leonard (Box 172, Folder 35)
      - Neame, Alan (Box 172, Folder 36)
      - Nemerov, Howard (Box 172, Folder 37)
      - Nemerov, Howard (Box 172, Folder 38)
      - Nims, John Frederick (Box 172, Folder 39)
      - Norse, Harold (Box 172, Folder 40)
      - O'Doherty, Brian (Box 172, Folder 41)
      - O'Gorman, Ned (Box 172, Folder 42)
      - O'Gorman, Ned (Box 172, Folder 43)
      - O'Gorman, Ned (Box 172, Folder 44)
      - O'Hara, Frank (Box 172, Folder 45)
      - O'Hara, Frank (Box 172, Folder 46)
      - Olson, Elder (Box 172, Folder 47)
      - Olson, Elder (Box 172, Folder 48)
      - Oppen, George (Box 172, Folder 49)
      - Page, P. K. (Box 173, Folder 1)
      - Parkinson, Thomas (Box 173, Folder 2)
      - Patchen, Kenneth (Box 173, Folder 3)
      - Patchen, Kenneth (Box 173, Folder 4)
      - Peachy, Frederic (Box 173, Folder 5)
      - Perret, Christopher (Box 173, Folder 6)
      - Perry, Ronald (Box 173, Folder 7)
      - Perry, Ronald (Box 173, Folder 8)
      - Petrie, Paul (Box 173, Folder 9)
      - Pillin, William (Box 173, Folder 10)
      - Plath, Sylvia (Box 173, Folder 11)
      - Pomeroy, Ralph (Box 173, Folder 12)
      - Pomeroy, Ralph (Box 173, Folder 13)
      - Ponsot, Marie (Box 173, Folder 14)
      - Posner, David L. (Box 173, Folder 15)
      - Raine, Kathleen (Box 173, Folder 16)
      - Raiziss, Sonia (Box 173, Folder 17)
      - Raiziss, Sonia (Box 173, Folder 18)
      - Read, Herbert (Box 173, Folder 19)
      - Rexroth, Kenneth (Box 173, Folder 20)
      - Rich, Adrienne (Box 173, Folder 21)
      - Ridler, Anne (Box 173, Folder 22)
      - Salinger, Herman (Box 173, Folder 23)
      - Salisbury, Ralph J. (Box 173, Folder 24)
      - Salomon, I. L. (Box 173, Folder 25)
      - Sandeen, Ernest (Box 173, Folder 26)
      - Sandeen, Ernest (Box 173, Folder 27)
      - Sarton, May (Box 173, Folder 28)
      - Schwartz, Delmore (Box 173, Folder 29)
      - Scott, Tom (Box 173, Folder 30)
      - Scott, Winfield Townley (Box 173, Folder 31)
      - Sexton, Anne (Box 173, Folder 32)
      - Shapiro, Karl (Box 173, Folder 33)
      - Shapiro, Karl (Box 173, Folder 34)
      - Singer, Helen (Box 173, Folder 35)
      - Sitwell, Edith (Box 173, Folder 36)
      - Smith, Sydney Goodsir (Box 173, Folder 37)
      - Smith, William Jay (Box 173, Folder 38)
      - Smith, William Jay (Box 173, Folder 39)
      - Solomon, Marvin (Box 173, Folder 40)
      - Squires, Radcliffe (Box 173, Folder 41)
      - Stafford, William (Box 173, Folder 42)
      - Stafford, William (Box 173, Folder 43)
      - Stafford, William (Box 173, Folder 44)
      - Stange, G. Robert (Box 173, Folder 45)
      - Stefanile, Felix (Box 173, Folder 46)
      - Stevens, Wallace (Box 173, Folder 47)
      - Stewart, Desmond (Box 173, Folder 48)
      - Stock, Robert (Box 173, Folder 49)
      - Strickhausen, Harry (Box 173, Folder 50)
      - Sward, Robert S. (Box 173, Folder 51)
      - Sweeney, John L. (Box 173, Folder 52)
      - Swenson, May (Box 173, Folder 53)
      - Tagliabue, John (Box 173, Folder 54)
      - Thomas, Dylan (Box 173, Folder 55)
      - Thompson, John (Box 173, Folder 56)
      - Tiempo, Edith (Box 173, Folder 57)
      - Todd, Ruthven (Box 173, Folder 58)
      - Tomlinson, Charles (Box 173, Folder 59)
      - Tomlinson, Charles (Box 173, Folder 60)
      - Tomlinson, Charles (Box 173, Folder 61)
      - Tomlinson, Charles (Box 173, Folder 62)
      - Trakl, George (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Triem, Eve (Box 174, Folder 2)
      - Tyler, Parker (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - Urdang, Constance (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - Van Duyn, Mona (Box 174, Folder 5)
      - Van Duyn, Mona (Box 174, Folder 6)
      - Vance Thomas (Box 174, Folder 7)
      - Vazakas, Byron (Box 174, Folder 8)
      - Wagner, Geoffrey (Box 174, Folder 9)
      - Wagoner, David (Box 174, Folder 10)
      - Wagoner, David (Box 174, Folder 11)
      - Wa-, Wakoski, Diane Walker, Mary Fraser (Box 174, Folder 12)
      - Walton, Eda Lou (Box 174, Folder 13)
      - Watkins, Vernon (Box 174, Folder 14)
      - Watkins, Vernon (Box 174, Folder 15)
      - Watson, James S. (Box 174, Folder 16)
      - Weiss, Neil (Box 174, Folder 17)
      - Weiss, Ted (Box 174, Folder 18)
      - Whittemore, Reed (Box 174, Folder 19)
      - Whittemore, Reed (Box 174, Folder 20)
      - Whittemore, Reed (Box 174, Folder 21)
      - Wilbur, Richard (Box 174, Folder 22)
      - Williams, William Carlos (Box 174, Folder 23)
      - Williams, William Carlos (Box 174, Folder 24)
      - Williams, William Carlos (Box 174, Folder 25)
      - Williams, William Carlos (Box 174, Folder 26)
      - Winters, Yvor (Box 174, Folder 27)
      - Winters, Yvor (Box 174, Folder 28)
      - Woods, John (Box 174, Folder 29)
      - Wright, David (Box 174, Folder 30)
      - Wright, James (Box 174, Folder 31)
      - Wright, James (Box 174, Folder 32)
      - Wright, James (Box 174, Folder 33)
      - Zaturenska, Marya (Box 174, Folder 34)
      - Zinnes, Harriet (Box 174, Folder 35)
      - Zukofsky, Louis (Box 174, Folder 36)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Publication Matter
      - 1954 January (Box 174, Folder 37)
      - 1954 January (Box 174, Folder 38)
      - 1954 January (Box 174, Folder 39)
      - 1954 January (Box 174, Folder 40)
      - 1955 January (Box 174, Folder 41)
      - 1955 March (Box 174, Folder 42)
      - 1955 March (Box 174, Folder 43)
      - 1955 September (Box 174, Folder 44)
      - 1956 February (Box 174, Folder 45)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Miscellaneous
      - Miscellaneous morgue data (Box 174, Folder 46)